<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Hitpoints and Himbos</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Hitpoints and Himbos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>blog@lordyod.com (Lord Yod)</managingEditor><webMaster>blog@lordyod.com (Lord Yod)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 14:58:50 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.lordyod.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Waterdeep Dragon Heist</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/waterdeep-dragon-heist/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 14:58:50 -0700</pubDate><author>blog@lordyod.com</author><dc:creator>Lord Yod</dc:creator><guid>https://www.lordyod.com/waterdeep-dragon-heist/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m running Waterdeep Dragon Heist using the Alexandrian Remix for a group of inexperienced players.
The party:
Blackberry Rabbitfoot, a halfling rogue. Of the six attack rolls she has made, 4 have been critical hits. She steals everything that isn&amp;rsquo;t nailed down. Sanghorn, an aasimar monk. He&amp;rsquo;s thought he was human his whole life, but recently started hearing from a spirit in his head, and has come to Waterdeep to find out what this means.</description></item><item><title>Beatrix the Monolith</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/beatrix/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 14:57:44 -0700</pubDate><author>blog@lordyod.com</author><dc:creator>Lord Yod</dc:creator><guid>https://www.lordyod.com/beatrix/</guid><description>Beatrix is a half-orc Gray Watchman Warden. In the Radiant Gaia setting, half-orcs are raised on stories of the heroism and valor of their orc ancestors, and Beatrix aspires to this. She believes strongly in the value of law and order, and had a promising career in the city watch before she had to give it up in order to pay off a gambling debt her lousy brother had built up.</description></item><item><title>Sinath Lonn</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/sinath-lonn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 14:56:26 -0700</pubDate><author>blog@lordyod.com</author><dc:creator>Lord Yod</dc:creator><guid>https://www.lordyod.com/sinath-lonn/</guid><description>This is a science fantasy campaign set in a homebrew world, run using a hacked version of 5th Edition D&amp;amp;D.
The current party:
Brisby, a halfling/goblin cleric from the mountains of the Mashioque Dynasty. They were raised by their adopted Dragonborn family and are not aware of their goblin heritage. They are a cleric of law and order, and are seeking their life&amp;rsquo;s purpose. Zo-zu, a human/goblin artificer from the Empire of Corus.</description></item><item><title>Hot Springs Island</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/hot-springs-island/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 14:56:10 -0700</pubDate><author>blog@lordyod.com</author><dc:creator>Lord Yod</dc:creator><guid>https://www.lordyod.com/hot-springs-island/</guid><description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m running the Hot Springs Island sandbox campaign by Jacob Hurst, using the Old School Essentials ruleset.
We&rsquo;re starting with the Classic ruleset, 3d6 in order. It&rsquo;s likely to be a very high-stakes game and this&rsquo;ll probably be a rude awakening for some of the players as they&rsquo;ve only had experience with 5e.
The party consists of a dwarf, a thief, a fighter, and two magic-users. So far the only thing we&rsquo;ve done is a session zero, it&rsquo;s scheduled to start next week.]]></description></item><item><title>Current RPGs</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/current-rpgs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 14:31:55 -0700</pubDate><author>blog@lordyod.com</author><dc:creator>Lord Yod</dc:creator><guid>https://www.lordyod.com/current-rpgs/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ll try to keep this post updated with a list of the games I&amp;rsquo;m currently running or playing in.
Playing Radiant Gaia: an open table 5th Edition D&amp;amp;D game set in a homebrew world, the players (mostly) come from an underground realm called Terra and are sent on expeditions to explore Gaia by a patron. I play Beatrix the Monolith, a half-orc Grey Watchman Warden. This game is run by Sammy who I met through the wonderful Alexandrian Discord.</description></item><item><title>Thoughts on A5e</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/thoughts-on-a5e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:48:03 -0700</pubDate><author>blog@lordyod.com</author><dc:creator>Lord Yod</dc:creator><guid>https://www.lordyod.com/thoughts-on-a5e/</guid><description><![CDATA[Level Up 5E advertises itself as &lsquo;advanced 5th edition&rsquo; and I&rsquo;ve had my eye on it for a while. While I haven&rsquo;t run any playtests I have read the material they&rsquo;ve released. I like a lot of the ideas that have have been introduced, such as increased martial class flexibility and an increased emphasis on the exploration pillar of play.]]></description></item><item><title>A wild blog appears</title><link>https://www.lordyod.com/a-wild-blog-appears/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>blog@lordyod.com</author><dc:creator>Lord Yod</dc:creator><guid>https://www.lordyod.com/a-wild-blog-appears/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Hi, I&rsquo;m Yod. I&rsquo;m starting this blog to share some thoughts on my interests.
This will probably be limited mostly to gaming and tech since those are the
things I generally feel the safest sharing with others, but who knows?</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>